Resume for Java Developer

General information

Name and Surname: Maksim Khortov Phone number: +1(718)710-7892 Address: Brooklyn, NY, USA Email: xoptov@gmail.com

Skype: xoptov

Date of birth: 10.07.1985

Desired position

For short-term purposes I would become a member of the team as developer. For long-term purposes I would become a team leader.

Goals

I going to finding interesting job in hakers team working on interesting project. I want increase my experience in Java World and taking more experience from development great and ambitious projects. The my main goal is laboriously work for the common good of the company and get satisfaction from their work. My second goal is increasing quality of their work.

Personal profile

- Responsibility;
- Sociability;
- Fast studying;
- Industry;
- Perfectionism.

Languages

- Russian(native);
- English(intermediate).

Experience

Category	Items
Programming languages	Java, JavaScript
Operation systems	FreeBSD, Debian, Ubuntu, Mac OSX
HTTP services	Glassfish, Tomcat
Frameworks	Java EE, Spring, Hibernate, Backbone.js, MarionetteJS, AngularJS
Databases	MySQL, PostgreSQL, MSSQL
Key Value storages	Redis, Memcache
Cache services	Varnish
IC services	Jenkins
AMPQ services	RabbitMQ, OpenMQ
Full text search engines	Elasticsearch, Sphinx
Testing	JUnit, Selenium, Phantomjs
Integration with	AWS S3, PayPal, Facebook, VK, Google
Version control systems	$\operatorname{git}, \operatorname{syn}$
Virtualization	VirtualBox, Vagrant
Test and bug trackers	Jira, RedMine

Career history

Company	Position	Period	OS	Languages
Linbo LLC	Team lead	Aug 2016 - Apr 2018	Linux	Java, JavaScript
Fin Service LLC	Developer	Jun 2015 - Aug 2016	Linux	Java, JavaScript
Clever-Web LLC	Team lead	Jun 2013 - May 2015	Linux, MacOSX	PHP, Java, JavaScript
Yug-Avto LLC	Developer	May 2012 - Jun 2013	$\operatorname{Linux},\operatorname{FreeBSD}$	PHP, JavaScript
RA Dom na Tamani	Developer	Jan 2011 - May 2012	${\rm Linux,\ FreeBSD}$	PHP, JavaScript
Japancaps.ru	Developer	$\rm Jul~2008$ - $\rm Jan~2011$	FreeBSD	PHP, JavaScript

Education

Period	Responsibilities
Feb 2014 - May 2014	Java 24-hours traning by Yakov Fine

Period	Responsibilities
Jun 2013 - Nov 2013	Synfony2 courses Middle Developer
Sep 2010 - Nov 2010	Networks and Linux courses
Sep 2006 - Jul 2009	Far Eastern Federal University, Computer Science
Sep 2003 - Jul 2008	Far Eastern Federal University, Physics and Computer Science

Interests

My hobbie reading book about new computer technologies. Learning a different approach in development.